let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Variable name in PHP starts with -",
        answer: "A. $ (Dollar)",
        options: [
           "A. $ (Dollar)",
            "B. ! (Exclamation)",
            "C. & (Ampersand)",
            "D. # (Hash)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "PHP stands for -",
        answer: "B. Hypertext Preprocessor",
        options: [
            "A. Personal Home Processor",
            "B. Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "C. Pretext Hypertext Preprocessor",
           "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: " Who is known as the father of PHP?",
        answer: "C. Rasmus Lerdrof",
        options: [
            "A. Drek Kolkevi",
            "B. List Barely",
            "C. Rasmus Lerdrof",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following is not a variable scope in PHP?",
        answer: "B. Extern",
        options: [
            "A. Global",
            "B. Extern",
            "C. Local",
            "D. Static"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following is correct to add a comment in php?",
        answer: "A. Both (b) and (c)",
        options: [
            "A. Both (b) and (c)",
            "B. // ……",
            "C./* …… */",
            "D. & …… &"
        ]
    },
   
        {
            numb: 6,
            question: "Which of the following is used to display the output in PHP?",
            answer: "D.Both (a) and (c)",
            options: [
               "A.print",
               "B.Write",
               "C.echo",
               "D.Both (a) and (c)"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 7,
            question: "Which of the following is the use of strlen() function in PHP?",
            answer: "A. The strlen() function returns the length of string",
            options: [
                "A. The strlen() function returns the length of string",
                "B. The strlen() function returns the type of string",
                "C. The strlen() function returns the value of string",
                "D. The strlen() function returns both value and type of string"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 8,
            question: " Which of the following is used for concatenation in PHP?",
            answer: "D. . (dot)",
            options: [
                "A. + (plus)",
                "B. append()",
                "C .Fixed",
                "D. . (dot)"
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 9,
            question: "Which of the following is the use of strpos() function in PHP?",
            answer: "B. The strpos() function is used to search for a character/text in a string",
            options: [
                "A. The strpos() function is used to search for a capitalize character in a string",
                "B. The strpos() function is used to search for a character/text in a string",
                "C. The strpos() function is used to search for a number in a string",
                "D.None of the above "
            ]
        },
        {
            numb: 10,
            question: "Which of the following is the correct way to create a function in PHP?",
            answer: "D. function myFunction()",
            options: [
                "A. New_function myFunction()",
                "B. Create myFunction()",
                "C. None of the above",
                "D. function myFunction()"
            ]
        }

    
];